(Sheldon:)to come up with
a theory of dark matter
(Sheldon:)that doesn't
make protons decay.
(Sheldon:)I'm hoping to
finally tackle it
by optimizing my
work environment.
(Sheldon:)See, I've got, uh, my tea is at
the perfect sipping temperature.
(Sheldon:)Uh, I have fleece-lined
boxer shorts
(Sheldon:)to keep my tushie toasty.
(Sheldon:)And then, oh,
last but not least,
(Sheldon:)this inspirational cat poster,
(Sheldon:)improved with
the reassuring face
(Sheldon:)of physics renegade
Richard Feynman.
(Penny:)Is that why you had to take him
to Office Depot last night?
(Leonard:)I don't want to talk about it.
(Leonard:)There, the place is all yours.
(Penny:)Yeah, have fun.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I will--
nothing more fun
(Sheldon:)than a paradigm-shifting
evening of science.
(scoffs)
(Penny:)And you thought it was
soaping me up in the shower.
(chuckles)
(Leonard:)Bye.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Here we go.
(Sheldon:)Proton decay.
LEONARD:
Hey, we're home.
(screams)
(Leonard:)Any progress?
How could there be?!
(Sheldon:)With these constant
interruptions.
(Penny:)I love him, but if he's broken,
let's not get a new one.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪